本字幕由 PTT同志影视作品板 2013重新校稿
原字幕取自网路资源  仅供学习 禁用任何商业盈利行为
校稿：hahanjia、AAA、mohiwa
同志亦凡人 Queer As Folk S01E16
哦  不
Oh, no!
那是干什麽
What is that about?
-我来付        -我来付  等等
-I got this.   -I got it. hang on.
-但我知道那是什麽意思      -是啊
-But I knew what it meant. -Yeah.
先生  这是你们的账单
There you go, sir.
我来付吧
I'll get that.
不用了  不用了
No, no, no, no, no.
不用  不用  不用
我来
I got it.
谢谢
Thank you.
迈克  不  不
Michael, no. no.
-不  我来付       -迈克
- No. I got this. -Michael!
-不    -谢谢
-No!   -thank you.
你还要什麽吗
Unless you want anything else
-是的  我要　　-甜点吗
-Yeah, I do.   -Dessert?
好孩子
Good boy.
黑森林蛋糕  两个叉子
Chocolate death,two forks
我不要甜点了
I don't want dessert.
那就一个叉子
One fork.
我要你别再抢着付帐
I want you to stop paying for everything.
-我不懂你的意思  　　　　　　　-你知道的
-I don't know what you mean.  -You know what I mean.
你总是在拿支票付钱
You're always picking up the cheque,
还有买电影票和日常杂货
And buying the movie tickets and getting the groceries.
-所以呢    -所以我是有工作的
-So?       -So I'm working.
不用你来养我
You don't have to support me.
我有能力付  你没有
I can afford it. you can't.
这有什麽大不了的
What's the big deal?
这对我来说很重要
It's a big deal to me.
我喜欢带你去好的地方  迈克
I like to take you nice places, Michael.
我也喜欢去啊  但是
And I like to go to them but...
我不喜欢一直都是你付帐
I don't like you paying for me all the time.
我  我感觉  很奇怪
I... I feel... funny.
你能负担的时候就让你付帐  行吗
You pay when you can, don't you?
好的  既然说到这个
Yeah, and speaking of which...
这个月的家用开支
This month's house expenses.
谢谢
Thank you.
-看到没  我现在在拿的是你的钱  -是吗
-See? I'm taking your money.   -Yeah.
一个月300块
$300 a month.
你确定这是一半的开销吗
You're sure that's half of everything?
当然了
Sure.
包括请清洁工和水电费
The cleaning lady? the utilities?
黑森林蛋糕来了
Chocolate death.
你要来一口吗
You want a bite?
「拉拉之夜」很有趣吧
Isn't "dyke nite" fun?
好久没这麽好玩了
Can't remember when I had such a good time.
我讨厌拉拉之夜
I hate "dyke nite".
我也是  我感觉被侵犯了
Me too. I feel so violated.
她们在干吗
Euw. what're they doing?
「拉拉调情」  你知道的
The "muncher mash"? You know...
茉儿
So, Mel,
你上次来「拉拉之夜」是多久之前？
When was the last time you were at "dyke nite"?
在我遇见琳赛之前
Oh, before I met Lindsay.
记住  我们说好了不提她的
Remember, we weren't going to mention her.
她很可爱
She's cute.
她让我想起红发的琳赛
She reminds me of Lindsay with red hair.
那她呢
What about her?
她让我想起黑发的琳赛
She reminds me of lindsay with black hair.
别告诉我
Don't tell me.
他让你想起变装的琳赛
He reminds you of Lindsay in drag.
我忍不住  就是想她
I can't help it. I miss her.
我以为我们能永远在一起
I thought we'd be together forever,
她就是我下半辈子
That she'd be the one I kissed good night
每晚睡前亲吻的人
for the rest of my life.
现在我和我堂妹丽塔住一起
Now I live with my cousin Rita,
每晚亲吻她说晚安
And kiss her good night.
老天
Christ!
听着  茉儿
Look, Mel,
和你一起玩很好
It's been great hanging with you.
你已经是一个很棒的腐女了
You've been a great fag-hag.
只是
Only the thing is;
腐女应该很开心的
Fag-hags are supposed to be fun.
为什麽你不去找琳赛
So why don't you go see Lindsay,
告诉她你的感受
Tell her how you feel,
然後跟她和好  好吗
And make up with her, okay?
在我做了那事之後  我还有脸去吗？
How can I do that after what I did?
不管你做了什麽
Whatever you did,
你要知道  这是两个人的事
You know, it takes two.
你没有什麽可失去的了
You got nothing to lose,
除非你还想等着下一次
Unless you really want to wait around for the next...
「来拉拉之夜」
"dyke nite". brrrr.
你喝了太多咖啡了
You drink too much coffee.
这不是咖啡  是拿铁
This isn't coffee. it's latte.
那就是5美元的咖啡
It's just coffee that costs five bucks.
还是会引起高血压
And it still causes high blood pressure,
心脏病发作  性功能下降
Heart attack, poor sexual performance.
没人抱怨过我的床上功夫
I haven't had any complaints.
更不用说失眠了
Not to mention insomnia.
反正通常我在床上也没睡觉
Well, usually when I'm in my bed, I'm not asleep anyway,
所以没关系
So it really doesn't matter.
知道吗  幸好我还很年轻
See, fortunately I have youth on my side.
我可以干上一整晚
I can stay up all night fucking
然後SAT考试照样拿1500分
And still score 1,500 on my S.A.T.S.
1500分
1,500?
-是的  -哇
-Yep.  -wow!
有那样的成绩
You could get into any school you wanted
你想进什麽学校都可以
With a score like that.
我申请了达特茅斯学院  布朗大学
I applied to Dartmouth, Brown...
你要到其他州去
You're going out of state?
怎麽了  你会在意吗？
Why? Do you give a shit?
只是我第一次听你说  仅此而已
It's just the first I've heard of it, that's all.
你在意！
You do!
你果然很在意！
You give a shit!
你真的很在意！
你在乎我 在乎得要死
You so care about me.
你爱我这麽多
You love me so much.
下车吧你
Get out!
布莱恩·肯尼很在乎我
Brian Kinney gives a shit.
-去你的    -哈哈
-Fuck you. -Ha-ha.
你看起来很爽嘛
Mmm! Well you look self-satisfied.
我都想用「目中无人」这句话了
I'd even go as far as to say supercilious.
我们都知道你词汇考了700分
We all know you got 700 verbal.
别卖弄了
Stop showing off.
所以 他刚对你说什麽了
So, what did he say to you?
是那些他没说出口的话
Hmm, it's what he didn't say.
让一下  死娘炮
Excuse me, faggot.
我不是娘炮
I'm not a faggot.
对我来说  你就是
You look like one to me.
你想吸我的老二吗
You wanna suck my cock?
天啊  他就不能想点新花样吗
Aw, christ! can't they think of anything more original to say?
别欺负他  赫伯
Leave him alone, Hobbs.
今天一定是同志大会
Oh, must be a faggot convention.
-不要发泄在他身上           -发泄什麽
-Don't take it out on him.  -Take what out?
你的老二
Your dick.
娘炮
Faggot.
你们两个　住手
Okay, you two, break it up.
马上
Now!
泰勒  你再惹麻烦的话
Taylor, next time you cause trouble,
就直接找校长报到吧
You can talk to the principal.
什麽
What?
老师  贾斯汀什麽都没做  是克里斯的错
Sir, Justin didn't do anything. it was Chris.
他叫他死娘炮
He called him a faggot.
坐好  你们两个都坐好
Take your seats. Both of you.
-布勒  　　-有
-Bueller.  -Here.
-查德斯  　　-有
-Chanders.   -Here.
-弗莱  　-有
-Frye.   -Here.
-冈德曼  　　-有
-Gunderman.  -Here.
-赫伯  　-有
-Hobbs.  -Here.
李普曼  你迟到了
Lipman, you're late.
-门德森 　　　-有
-Mendelson.   -Here.
-罗伊斯  -有
-Ruis.   -Here.
-泰勒  　　-娘娘到
-Taylor.   -Queer.
同学们  安静  汤玛斯
Okay, class, quiet down. Thomas.
不好意思  迪克生先生
Excuse me, Mr. Dixon?
什麽事  泰勒
What is it, Taylor?
克里斯刚刚骂我
Chris just called me queer.
我什麽都没听到
I didn't hear anything.
你怎麽可能没听到  大家都听到了
How could you not hear it? Everybody heard that.
坐下  泰勒
Sit down, Taylor.
我要他道歉
I want him to apologize.
我说了  坐下
I said sit down.
你打算什麽都不做吗
Aren't you going to do anything?
就这麽假装什麽都没发生
Are you just going to pretend that nothing happened?
你再说一句就把你送到校长办公室去
One more word from you and I'm sending you to the principal's office.
不麻烦你了
Huh! Don't bother.
娘娘起驾了  娘娘要出门了
The queer's going. the queer is out the door.
娘娘要离开了
The queer is gone.
够了
That's enough of that.
你知道什麽
Oh! What do you know?
他刚说了  你就什麽都没听到
He says it,you don't hear a thing.
但我说了
But when I say it...
既然你听力恢复了  就给我听好
Well, listen up, now that your hearing has returned.
这个娘娘说「干你娘的！」
This queer says, "fuck you!"
好的  够了  泰勒  你给我出去
Okay, that's it, Taylor. you are out of here.
下一位
Next customer, please.
你好  我是保罗
Hi, I'm Paul. uh...
如果你今天在我们这儿开一个理财帐户
If you open up a money market account with us today,
你就会得到一张50美元的
You'll get a $50 gift certificate
雷射除毛礼券
For laser hair removal.
谢了  我用蜜蜡除毛
Thanks. I wax.
我刚刚看了一下我的户头
Um, I was just looking at my statement,
除非是我不知道自己加薪了
And unless I got a raise that nobody told me about,
我的帐户多了很多
Um, there's a lot more money in my chequing account
不属於我的钱
than there should be.
刷一下你的卡然後输入密码
Oh. uh, just swipe your card and enter your pin number.
等你忙完我朋友的帐
When you're finished helping my friend,
可以帮我检查一下户头吗
Could you check the balance in my account?
当然可以
Sure.
麻烦写一下你的帐号
Do you want to put down the number?
这是你的电话
This is your phone number.
你可以先让他帮我
Would you please let him help me
处理完我的户头
with my financial problem
然後再处理你的龟头  好吗
Before you hit on him?
-你多了多少钱  　　　　　　　　　 -将近一千块
-So how much extra do you have?   -Almost 1,000.
哇~ 你最好常出现这种财务问题
Well, you should always have such financial problems.
看来你签出的一些支票没有被兑现
It appears some of your cheques haven't cleared.
哪些
Which ones?
566号和574号
Number 566, 574.
还有583号
583?
那个也是
That one too.
谢谢了
Well, thanks.
至少我知道问题出在哪儿了
Well, at least I know what the discrepancy is.
大卫根本没有兑现我的支票
David isn't cashing my cheques.
也许他忘了
Well, maybe he forgot.
他那种年纪很健忘的
You know how people are when they get to be his age.
走吧
Come on, let's go.
-我会给你打电话的　　　　　　-太好了
-I'll check this out, sir.  - Excellent.
还是有些服务  ATM是提供不了的
There are still certain services you can't get at an ATM.
琳
Linz...
茉儿
Mel...
我来看看盖斯  还有
I, um, came by to see Gus and...
琳  我想死你了
Oh, Linz, I miss you so much.
我一直在等你说这句话
I've waited so long to hear you say that.
真抱歉  亲爱的
I'm sorry, baby.
这一切我都很抱歉
I'm so sorry for everything.
我也是  谁的错都无所谓了
Me too. And it doesn't matter whose fault it was.
唯一重要的是  我们
Now all that matters... is this.
嗯（发音同"we"）
Oui?
「我们」
"we"?
「嗯」
"Oui".
意思是「有什麽事吗」
As in, "is there something you would like?"
实际上
Uh, actually...
对  我找琳赛
Yes. I'd like to see Lindsay.
琳赛现在不在
Ah, Lindsay is not here right now.
她在给别人上课
She's teaching class.
你是谁
And who are you?
我是吉拉姆  你是谁
I am Guillaume. And you are...?
茉蕾妮
Melanie.
啊  茉蕾妮  她的前女友
Ah, Melanie, the ex-girlfriend.
你知道我是谁
You know who I am?
你是那个出轨的人
You're the one who had the affair.
在法国的话  这当然不算什麽
Of courseen France, this would be meaningless.
我不相信她都告诉你了
I-I can't believe she told you that.
琳赛和我很亲密
Lindsay and I are very, uh, intime.
-亲密  　　　-我明白了
-Intimate.   -I got it.
我来看我儿子
Look, I stopped by to see my son.
我觉得不太方便  现在是他的用餐时间
Mmm. I-I'm afraid it's not possible. It's his feeding time.
-我可以  　　　　　　　-不不不
-Well, I could do...   -No, no, no. no.
我来就可以了  他很  呃
I will do it. He gets very, um...
怎麽说呢  他很挑剔
What you call it? uh, Finicky.
好吧  你他妈到底是谁
Okay. Who the fuck are you anyway,
为什麽琳赛从来没跟我说过你
and why hasn't Lindsay ever told me about you?
也许她不想告诉你
Perhaps it's her decision,
既然你们没住一起了
now that you're no longer living together,
就没必要和你分享她的生活细节
Not to share with you all the details of her life.
这很正常
This is normal.
我来了  我的小亲亲
I'm on my way, mon petit chou.
我会告诉她你来过了
So, I tell her you stop by.
既然大卫不去兑现我的支票
Why would David keep taking my cheques
为什麽他要收下呢
If he has no intention of cashing them?
也许他在等下一季
Well, maybe he's waiting until next quarter
等他不够钱交税的时候再说
When he has less tax liability.
真像会计师该说的话
Spoken like a true accountant.
也许他只是为了让你开心
Or maybe he's just taking them to humour you.
我可一点都开心不起来
Well, I'm not amused.
我有能力付钱
I can pay my own way.
-很高尚  　　　-还很蠢
-Very noble.   -Yeah, and stupid!
迈克  亲爱的
Michael, sweetie,
所有同志的梦想就是被人包养
It's every gay boy's dream to be a kept woman.
她在这儿干什麽
What's she doing in here?
-天啊  　　　　-你觉得我以前没看过老二吗
-Oh, christ!   -Do you think I've never seen a dick before?
没看过我的
Not mine!
没事的  没事的大家
It's okay. It's okay, everyone.
她是个拉子
She's a lesbian.
哦  她是个女同
Oh, she's a dyke.
茉蕾妮  你来这儿干什麽
Melanie, what are you doing here?
我听了你的建议  跑去找琳赛
I took your advice and I went to go see Lindsay.
你最後一次和她说话是什麽时候
Uh, when was the last time you talked to her?
几周之前
A couple of weeks.
她跟你提过一个法国佬吗
Did she mention anything about a French guy?
没有
No.
法国佬？
A french guy?
我过去找她
I went over to see her,
这个混蛋法国猪来开门
And this fucking frog answered the door.
-所以呢  -所以当我想看看盖斯时
-So?     -So when I tried to see gus,
他妈的把门甩在我脸上
He slammed the god- damn door in my face.
所有人都知道
Well, every- body knows
法国人以闪电泡芙
The French are famous for eclairs,
口交和粗鲁闻名
Oral sex and rudeness.
我之前约过一个男的 三样齐全
I once had a date that involved all three.
也许她只是找了个保姆
Maybe she just got herself a babysitter.
从法国吗
From France?
她上课的薪水可付不起
A little pricey on her teacher's salary.
而且她怎麽都没跟我们提过
And how come she didn't tell us about it?
你好（法语）
Bonjour.
听听这个
H-hey, listen to this.
这是琳赛和吉拉姆家
You have reached Lindsay and Guillaume
还有可爱宝宝盖斯
And beautiful baby Gus.
如果你有事找我们
If you have a message for us,
请在哔声後留言
Kindly leave it after the beep.
「我们」
"Us."
对保姆来说真是过头了
It's pretty pushy for the help.
听起来他们像对夫妻
It makes it sound like they're a couple.
这样可是违背了犹太律法
Quelque chose isn't kosher.
你知道我上次拿
You know the last time I brought
热巧克力和饼乾上来是什麽时候吗
hot chocolate and fig newtons up here?
当迈克还住在这的时候
When Michael lived here?
真聪明
Smart kid. Hmmm.
他锁上房门待了好久
He'd lock himself in here for hours and hours.
告诉我他在玩模型飞机
Told me he was playing with his model airplanes.
我当然知道他在玩什麽
Ha! I know what he was playing with.
喏
Here.
想吃吗
You want one?
不了  谢谢
No thanks.
老师这样做真糟糕
It's a lousy thing that teacher did,
害你被停学
Having you suspended.
我应该一拳打在那个迪克生的鸡巴脸上
Yeah, I could punch dickhead Dixon's face in.
还有克里斯·赫伯
Chris Hobbs' too.
如果你做了  你就和他们一样了
Only then, you'd be just like them.
那又怎麽样
So what?
-他们活该被打  　　-他们的确是
-They deserve it.  -Sure they do.
但是有更好的方法来解决
But there are better ways of handling it.
退学吗
Huh, quit school?
让他们高兴吗
And give them the pleasure?
那些人
There were people...
当他们知道迈克是同志後
When they found out that Michael was gay...
说了和做了最残忍的事情
Who said, and did, the cruelest things.
朋友
Friends...
邻居
Neighbours...
家人
Family.
我姐姐甚至不让她的孩子过来玩
My own goddamn sister wouldn't even let her kids come over here.
她怕迈克会骚扰她的孩子
She was afraid Michael was going to molest them or something.
因为人们就是会这样
Because that's the way people are.
他们很无知  很害怕
They're ignorant and they're scared.
而你完全无能为力
And there's nothing you can do...
只能教育他们或者打死他们
Except educate 'em or shoot 'em.
我加入了同志老妈联盟  因为我觉得
Me, I joined P-FLAG, 'cause I figured
这比打死他们更实际
It was more practical than shooting 'em.
你学校有同志社团吗
Do you have a gay club at your school?
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
常有人这麽说我
I've been accused of it.
不  我应该是学校唯一的同志学生
No. I'm, like, the only gay student there.
我可不信  阳光小子
I doubt that, sunshine.
同志小孩到处都有
Gay kids are everywhere.
只是他们和你不一样
Only they're not all like you...
因为他们害怕被人发现道
'cause they're afraid to show their faces.
这就是为什麽
That's why maybe...
你应该做点什麽去帮助他们　让他们了解
You've got to do something to help them know that...
他们并不孤单
They're not the only ones.
我没有兑现支票是因为我用不到你的钱
I didn't cash your cheques because I don't need your money.
但是我得付给你
But I need to give it to you.
迈克  你知道
Michael, you know, of course,
每个月的一半开销不只是三百块
That half the monthly expenses aren't really $300.
我当然知道  我还知道不管是多少
Of course I know, and I'm sure whatever it is,
我都付不起  但是这不是重点
I couldn't afford it, but that's not the point.
-我想尽量帮点忙　  　　　　　　　　　　　　　-你帮了
-Uh, I want to contribute as much as I can. - And you do.
你帮了  你给了我比金钱更贵重的东西
You do. You give me something much more valuable than money.
你给了我你的可爱
You give me your sweetness,
你的迷人  你的幽默和你性感的小屁股
Your charm, your humour, your hot little butt.
我是说  付一半的水电瓦斯费
I mean, what's paying half the gas and electric
怎麽能和这个比  迈克
Compared to that, Michael?
我可不是你的金屋藏娇
I'm not some boytoy you're keeping.
我从来没这麽想过  别这样羞辱我
I've never thought of you as my boytoy. Don't insult me.
给我吧
I'll take that.
好的
Okay.
只要你高兴随你怎麽做  随你要什麽
Okay, whatever will make you happy. Whatever you want.
我只要你收下我的钱
What will make me happy is if you...
然後别老抢着付帐
Take my money and you stop paying for everything.
好吧  从此以後我们只做
Fine. From now on, we'll only do things
我们都可以负担得起的事
That we can both afford to do, together.
还有一件事
There's only one thing.
什麽
What's that?
别生气  本来应该是个惊喜的
Don't get mad. It was supposed to be a surprise.
但是
But you know that...
你放假的那周
The week that you have off from work?
我自己也安排了休假  我订了
I cleared it for me too, and I popped for...
去巴黎的行程
A trip to Paris.
头等舱  乔治五世酒店套房
First-class, suite at the hotel "Georges V".
还预订了最好的餐馆
Reservations at all the finest restaurants.
哇塞
Wow. That...
听起来太棒了
That sounds fantastic.
-我知道  　-但是
-I know.   -But...
不  我知道  我知道
No, I know. I know.
我又做错事了
It was the wrong thing to do. I'll, uh...
明天我会取消它
Cancel it tomorrow.
我们就待在家里  看部电影
And we'll just stay home, watch a movie...
或者两部也行  在家自己做饭吃
Or two, eat in.
这样也不错
And that can still be fun.
嗨  琳赛
Hi, Lindsay.
希望你不介意我们就这样找上门
Hope you don't mind us all dropping by like this.
其实你们可以先打个电话
Actually, you could have called.
打了  但是转到了语音信箱
We did, and got your message.
看看谁来了
Look who's here.
看看还有谁来了
Ah. Look who else is here.
这是吉拉姆
This is Guillaume.
我想你应该见过茉蕾妮
I believe you've met Melanie.
茉蕾妮  你好吗（法语）
Oui. Melanie, comment ca va?
你好吗
Um, how are you?
还好
Uh, ca va just fine.
这是布莱恩  盖斯的亲生父亲
This is Brian, Gus' biological father.
哦
Ah oui.
啊  我的朋友  放心吧
Oh. Be assured, my friend,
现在我在这  就不用担心盖斯了
There's no need to worry about Gus now that I'm here.
你在这我才更担心  我的朋友（法语）
Mm-hm. I wasn't worried when you weren't... Mon ami.
这是泰德和艾美特
And this is Ted and Emmett.
你好（法语）
Bonjour.
晚上好（法语）
Bonsoir.
很高兴认识你（法语）
Enchante.
我们正在吃晚饭
We were just in the middle of dinner,
所以如果你们不介意的话
So if you don't mind...
如果你想的话  你朋友们可以跟我们一起吃
Uh, i-if you would like, your friends may join us.
应该有足够的兔肉
There's enough... rabbit for everyone.
兔肉吗
R-rabbit?
是的  我炖了一锅
Yes, I made a, uh, stew.
炖的兔肉吗
With... with rabbit?
-兔子肉吗  　　　-据说味道像鸡肉
-Bunny rabbit?   -They say it tastes just like chicken.
请过来  尝一些吧
Please, uh, come, try some.
就尝一点吧
Well, maybe just a... little taste.
我有一点饿  所以
I'm... I'm a little hungry, so, uh...
发生什麽事了
What's going on?
对啊  这个男的是谁
Yeah. Who's this guy?
还有他在我们家干什麽
And what's he doing in our house?
不好意思  我不喜欢你们直接闯进来
Excuse me, I don't appreciate your barging in here
质问我
And interrogating me.
谁在质问你啊
Oh-ho, whoa. Who's interrogating you?
我们只是问问
We're just asking you.
吉拉姆在大学教法语
Guillaume teaches french at the university.
我们认识几年了
We've been friends for a couple of years.
那你怎麽从来都没提起过他
Yeah well, how come you never mentioned him?
我提过的
I did.
只是你从来都没听进去
You just never listened.
不管怎麽样
Huh. Anyway,
我们可以各取所需
He needed some help, and so did I.
所以我就让他搬进来了
So I said he could move in.
那你怎麽不告诉我们呢
So why didn't you tell us?
我们最近不是都没联络了吗
We haven't exactly been communicating lately.
我的天哪
Oh, my god!
这真是太好吃了
This is fabulous! Magnifique!
这是我有生以来吃过最棒的兔肉
It's the best rabbit I've ever had.
也是头一次吃
The only rabbit I've ever had.
对  他是个很棒的厨师
Yeah, he's a... fantastic cook,
他照顾小孩也很厉害
And he's wonderful with the baby.
盖斯马上就喜欢他了
And Gus took to him immediately.
而且有他帮忙还房贷
And I can't tell you what a relief it is
让我轻松了不少
Having him help with the mortgage.
听起来真是完美的安排啊
Sounds like the perfect arrangement.
那他还要住多久
So how long is he staying?
那要看情况
That all depends.
直到他找到自己的栖身之所吗
Until he finds a place of his own?
直到....  我们结婚
Until... We get married.
什麽
What?
你疯了吗
Are you fucking nuts?
不要太激动了  只是权宜之计
Don't get so excited. It's just an arrangement.
我能多个帮手
I can get some help,
他可以留在美国  领到绿卡
And he can stay in the country and get his green card.
我认为你们应该快点来吃（法语）
Alors, I must insist that you come eat tout de suite,
不然都凉了
Or else it gets cold.
他说那些话  感觉像在暗示
The way he insinuated himself...
对  就像...那是他的房子  他住那里
Right. Like... like... it was his house...That he belongs there...
而你和我  反而像陌生人
And you and I were like a couple of strangers.
我很想哈一支烟
I need a cigarette, bad.
这全都是我的错
This is all my fault.
如果不是我  这一切就不会发生了
If it weren't for me, none of this would be happening.
受折磨的茉蕾妮
Oh, Melanie the martyr.
要我帮你「点火」吗？
You want me to set you on fire?
混蛋  借我个火
Asshole, just gimme a light.
如果她真要这麽做
And if she goes through this,
他会在那住个几年
He's going to have to live there for at least a couple of years.
到那时盖斯就会吸高卢烟(法国香烟)
And by then Gus'll be smoking Gauloises and...
还不抹体香剂
Not wearing deodorant.
然後她会继续她的新生活
And she'll have moved on with her life.
那我们就不可能再在一起了
There's no way we'll ever get back together.
除非让她知道
If only she knew
她会因此惹上多少麻烦
How much trouble she could get into;
我知道琳赛自己可能不太在意
Well, knowing Lindsay... probably wouldn't care.
她总是很照顾其他人
She's always looking out for the welfare of others.
她是很大方的人
The generous one.
而我总是自私的
Then there's me, the selfish one.
我只是想上床  然後就只是打炮
I wanted a fuck, and boy, did I get fucked.
满足自己的需求不算有错啊
There's nothing wrong with getting your needs met.
从你口中说出来可不新鲜啊
That's no surprise coming from you.
几乎是你的座右铭
It's your manifesto.
这不是我专属的  如果每个人都勇於承认
Well, it would be everyone's if they were honest enough to admit it.
别再自责啦  很烦啊
So stop blaming yourself. It's boring.
关键不是你的错
And you don't deserve it.
-嗨    -嗨
-Hey!  -Hey.
明天不是有课吗?  你应该在黛比家念书吧?
Isn't it a school night? Shouldn't you be at Deb's studying?
-我被勒令停学了    -你?
-I got suspended.  - You?
停两天
For two days.
我看到一个学生被侮辱
I saw this student getting bashed,
我那恐同的老师只是在一旁看着...
And my homophobic teacher wouldn't do anything about it...
所以我叫他他妈的滚远一点
So I told him to fuck off.
全班榜样啊
Go to the head of the class.
这可勾起不少回忆
That brings back memories,
在操场上被打的半死不活
Getting the shit kicked out of you on the playground.
在更衣室里被燃着的火柴砸过来
Mmm. Having... lit matches thrown at you in the locker room.
美好的时光
Good times. Yeah.
我可没想过你也遇过
I don't suppose anything like that ever happened to you.
有一次一个橄榄球员抓住我
Well, once this straight football jock picked me up,
按住我的头往马桶里浸
And dunked my head in the toilet.
那你怎麽办?
What did you do?
我跟踪他到衣柜
I followed him to his locker.
衣柜门打开的  他的手像这样伸开
It was open, his hand was up kind of like this;
他正在大笑
He was laughing;
我猛地把门甩上  他就断了三根手指
So I slammed the door so hard it broke three of his fingers.
他那一季都不能出赛了
And that was the end of the season for him.
一个「同男-直男」什麽?
A gay-straight what?
「异同学生联盟」
Student alliance.
这是什麽鬼东西?
What the fuck is that?
一个社团
It's a club,
一个讨论问题然後举办活动的社团
A forum where students discuss issues, plan events.
你知道   促进互相了解
You know, to promote understanding.
我快睡着了
I'm asleep already.
我需要你的专家见解
I need your expertise.
我已经教你很多了
I think I've given you plenty.
你的工作专才
Your business expertise.
这可没什麽市场  尤其在圣詹姆士中学
It's a tough sell, especially at St. James.
如果我去你办公室  跟你提出这个概念
So, say I brought this concept to you at your office.
你会怎麽行销它?
How would you market it?
现在是凌晨1点30分
It's 1:30 in the morning,
而且我慾火焚身
And I'm horny as hell.
拜托
Please?
好
Okay.
你当顾客
You're the client.
泰勒先生  请坐
Have a seat, Mr. Taylor.
有什麽好笑?
Well, what's so funny?
我都是这样幻想我的顾客
You know, that's just how I imagine all my clients.
幻想他们一丝不挂
I picture them naked.
我真不敢相信我在做这件事
I can't believe I'm doing this.
好吧
Okay.
你有这个"异同学生联盟"的想法
So you have this concept, the gay-straight student alliance.
让我们活在当下
Let's all live together.
赋予人们权利  和平  有够无聊的
Power to the people. Peace. That's boring as shit.
我可以拿把乌兹冲锋枪扫射人群
I could take out an UZI and shoot everyone.
那还让人兴奋一点
That would be exciting.
起码你引起人家注意了
Well, at least you'd get their attention.
我们要想个推销它的好点子
Now we have to figure out a way to sell it.
对啊  要怎麽做呢?
Right. How?
-跟推销其他东西的办法一样：「性」              -性?
- The same way you sell everything else. Sex.  -Sex?
想让他们参与  就发给他们这个
You want to get 'em in the tent. Hand out these.
保险套?
Condoms?
你说是个联盟
You said it was an alliance.
除了这个还有什麽更能吸引他们的?
What better way for everyone to come together?
他想带你去巴黎?
He wants to take you to Paris?
亲爱的  你真是全世界最幸运的人啊
Honey, you're the luckiest boy in the world.
把糖浆递给我
Pass me the syrup.
我超爱巴黎的
I love Paris.
你又没去过巴黎
You've never been to Paris.
我知道我到了那  绝对会爱上那里
Well, I know I'll love it when I get there.
那你们什麽时候动身?
So when are you leaving?
不去了
We're not.
你说什麽(法语)
Excusez-moi?
我又没那麽多钱  享受那种旅行
I don't have the money for that kind of a trip.
你是付不起  可大卫付得起啊
Of course you don't. But David does.
我告诉他  我不能让他替我付钱
I told him I couldn't let him pay for me.
你是不是脑子烧坏了?
Are you completely mad?
你当然可以让他请客
Of course you can.
大卫和我达成了一项协议
David and I have an arrangement.
我们只进行一些双方都能担负得起的活动
We only do things that we can both afford.
巴黎,别了！  匹兹堡,您好！
Au revoir, Paris. Bonjour, pittsburgh.
我虽然没机会看见塞纳河的日落
All right, so I won't get to see the Seine at sunset,
也不能在卢森堡的公园散步
Or... or stroll through the Luxembourg gardens,
他计划好的其他超棒的事也泡汤了  但至少...
Or any of the other wonderful stuff he had planned, but at least...
你维护了你的「尊严」 (衣服品牌)
You'll have your pride?
我听说
Ah. I hear it's what
巴黎今年很流行这牌子
Everyone is wearing in Paris this year.
大卫带我去吃晚餐
David already takes me to dinner,
买日常用品
He buys the groceries.
付担所有家计
He pays all the house expenses.
这种好事到哪找?
Where do I sign up?
这是不对的
It's not right.
可如果那是他心甘情愿的呢?
But if he wants to do it?
他也是这麽说的  他说这让他很开心
That's what he says. He says it makes him happy.
那你就别他妈的这麽自私了
Then stop being so goddamn selfish.
自私?
Selfish?
不满足他的需求就是自私
I think it's selfish to deny your lover pleasure.
听我说  迈克  钱的事我可是专家
Listen to me, Michael. Money is my business.
我见过很多为了钱分手的情侣
I've seen it destroy more relationships than sex.
现在  你觉得这种维护假尊严的行为
Okay? Now you think you're being fair to David
对大卫来说是一种公平
With this false pride thing of yours,
可这只会造成他怨怼和伤心
But it'll only cause resentment and frustration.
而且坦白地说  你也剥夺了自己
And frankly, you're denying yourself the opportunity
看看外面世界的机会
To go places that you could never go,
还有尝试其他新鲜事物的机会
And do things you could never do.
就像芭芭拉在「你好！多莉」里 (电影主题曲)
It's like what Barbra said so eloquently
尖锐地说着
In "hello, dolly!",
即使当时她还太年轻不适合演那角色
Even though she was years too young for the part.
「钱就像是肥料」
"Money is like manure.
「不把它洒遍各地  让它推动事物发展」
It isn't worth a thing unless you spread it around,
「它就什麽都不是」
encouraging things to grow.
「明白了吗?」
Ya know what I mean?"
亲一个  贺瑞斯
Kiss me, Horace.
放学之後有一个
There's a meeting after school
「异同学生联盟」的集会
of the gay-straight student alliance.
放学之後有一个集会
Uh... uh, after school there's a meeting...
「异同学生联盟」
The gay-straight student alliance.
-要不要一个免费保险套?        -好啊
-Hey, you want a free condom? -Oh, yeah.
来  从这里拿一个
Here, you gotta take one of these then.
-酷啊  谢了    -这给你
-Cool. Thanks. - Here.
不错   这给你
Sure. Here you go.
放学之後有一个集会
Um, there's a meeting after school,
请拿一个免费保险套  还有传单
Please take a free condom and a flyer.
布莱恩还真有一套
Brian knows what he's talking about.
-是啊  他很聪明          -而且火辣
- Yeah, he's brilliant.  -And hot!
可以给我一个保险套吗?
Can I have a condom?
当然可以
Sure. um...
你好  泰勒
Hey, Taylor,
你创办一个「塞康社」吗?
You starting a faggot club?
不论同志还是直男  都可以参加
It's for gay students and straight students.
为了让两个群体互相尊重  互相理解
To promote tolerance and understanding.
这麽说插人屁眼是社团课程罗?
So now butt- fucking is an extracurricular activity?
不是  只是打手枪而已
No, just hand-jobs.
你最好永远别提起那件事  你这个吸屌男
You better never mention that again, you little cocksucker.
我承认这事有点疯狂
I admit it's a little crazy.
疯狂?  如果是钱的问题
Crazy? You know, if this is about money,
我告诉过你  我可以帮你
I told you I'd help you out.
你已经帮很多忙了
And you have.
我得学着自己处理
But I got to start taking care of myself.
我不能永远指望着你和茉蕾妮
I mean, I can't keep relying on you and Melanie.
好吧  但你非得和他结婚吗?
Okay, but do you have to fucking marry him?
就做做样子而已  只是个协议
But it's not a real marriage. It's just an arrangement.
那他最好想个别的协议
Well, he should arrange something else.
如果他是直人的话  他可以和某人邂逅
If he was straight, he could meet someone,
坠入爱河  然後结婚
Fall in love and get married.
但因为他是同志  现在无法达成
But because he's gay, there's no way.
而且这对双方都不公平
And that's not fair.
真是理直气壮  义愤填膺
Well, listen to the righteous indignation.
倒是挺像我之前认识的琳赛
Kinda sounds like the Lindsay I used to know.
是吗  过去的琳赛是什麽时候?
Oh, yeah, which Lindsay was that?
大四你变成  疯狂搞政治活动的拉拉
The last year of college when you turned into that scary political dyke.
她啊  那个写请愿书
Oh, her. The one who started the petition
建议对约会强暴犯  处以阉割处罚的琳赛
to make date-rape punishable by castration.
我还让你签名了
I even got you to sign.
是啊  你总是从事那些崇高的事
Yeah, well, you always were one for a worthy cause.
那个  小茉和我一直在考虑
Listen, Mel and I've been thinking...
等等
Wait a minute.
你刚是不是说了
Did I just hear you say...
「小茉和我?」
"Mel and I"?
你真这麽说吗?
Did you actually say that?
这些年来  我一直努力
Years I have struggled
让你和小茉和平共处
To get Mel and you to be civil to each other,
哪怕让你们能和平同处一室也行
even be in the same room together.
现在可好  小茉和你同一战线了?
Now all of a sudden, Mel and you are allies?
我可没时间管我那群自私
Well, I don't have time to worry about what my selfish,
自我中心  而且自恋的朋友们想什麽
Self-centred, narcissistic friends think.
我得全心放在我儿子身上
I have to think about my son,
想想我怎麽抚养他  支持他
And how I'm going to raise and support him.
我得想想什麽对他是最好的
I have to think about what's best for him.
所以我觉得  你最好还是他妈滚开！
So I think you should just fuck off.
我觉得你可以理解的
I'm sure that's a thought you can understand.
我还以为来的人会更多呢  你不觉得吗?
I thought a lot more people would come, didn't you?
那些保险套都被拿光了
I mean, considering all the condoms we handed out.
是啊  我猜他们迫不及待想戴上它
Yeah. I guess they couldn't wait to use them.
嘿
Hey!
来的人不少啊
Not a bad turnout, huh?
黛比  你来这儿干嘛啊
Deb, wh... what are you doing here?
我想你们需要些饼乾  并表达精神上的支持
Well, I thought you could use some cookies and moral support.
来点饼乾吧  孩子们
Here you go, kids. huh?
别客气
Enjoy yourselves.
手工烤的
Home-baked.
我的姑姑费怡曾在一个歌舞团表演过
My great-aunt Fay, who was in burlesque,
她说永远不要在一群饥肠辘辘的观众面前表演
said you should never go on in front of a hungry audience.
我们是不是得开始了
Well, I guess we should get started, huh?
好吧
Well...
祝你好运  小阳光
Good luck, sunshine. hmm?
你也是  达芙妮  征服他们吧
You too, Daphne. knock 'em dead.
请大家安静一下
Could we have your attention? Please?
谢谢
Thank you.
你们好  我是达芙妮
Hi. um, I'm Daphne.
欢迎来到圣詹姆斯学校 「异同学生联盟」的
Welcome to the first meeting of the St. James
第一次集会
Gay-straight student alliance.
接下来的几周里  我们会讨论一些
In the upcoming weeks, we will be discussing issues
圣詹姆斯学校里  与所有人有关的议题
that affect all of us here at st. James...
这社团不是谈性的吗?
Isn't this supposed to be about sex?
性只是一部份
Sex is part of it.
也有一些别的事情
But it's also about other things.
比如我们怎麽看待自己  怎麽看待他人
Like how we see ourselves and each other.
算了吧  我们走吧
Fuck this. let's go.
屁精
Faggot!
吸屌男!  同性恋!
Cocksucker! Homo!
甲甲! 统塞康!
Fudge-packer!
我之前曾被人这麽叫过
Those are a few of the names that I have been called
就因为我是同性恋
Because I'm gay.
也有人跟我说  我会下地狱
I've also been told that I'm going to hell,
还说我会染上爱滋而死
And that I should die of aids.
也许你们也遇到过类似的情况
Maybe the same thing has happened to you.
这就是我们聚在这里的原因
That is why we're here...
试着接受我们  彼此的不同
To see if we can learn to accept our differences
并了解我们相同之处
And recognize our similarities.
不管是同志还是异性恋  我们的初衷都是一样
Because gay or straight, we all want the same things.
好吧  泰勒  闹够了
All right, Taylor, that's enough.
我们只是开个会...
We're... we're just having a meeting.
你得到校长的允许了吗?
Did you get permission from the principal?
你有申请用这间教室吗?  你们有指导老师吗?
Did you ask to use this classroom? Do you have an advisor?
他有我
He's got me.
你是谁?
And who are you?
黛比·瓦特尼  你又是谁?
Debbie Novotny. Who are you?
我是学校的教职员
I'm a member of the faculty.
那你应该很高兴看到
Well then, you'll be happy to know
我们正在进行一堂很有教育意义的课程
that we're having a little educational program here.
你坐下来听听吧
So why don't you sit down?
也许会有所收获呢
You might learn something.
这也是你课程的一部份吗?
Is this part of your curriculum?
废什麽话  当然是
You bet your ass it is.
现在  所有人都离开这  会议结束了
Now, all of you, on your way. This meeting is over.
快点  离开
Come on. Let's go.
做的不错  同学
Yeah, nice try, man. Yeah.
-再见  贾斯汀      -再见  达芙妮
-See you, Justin.  -See you, Daphne.
别放弃  达芙妮
Try again, Daphne.
干
Fuck.
真是辛苦的一周
Man, it's been a long week.
我真想抽时间放松一下
I am really looking forward to taking some time off.
明天早上七点半还有个病人
Got a patient at 7:30.
晚安
Good night.
-大卫    -怎麽了?
-David?  -Yes?
你觉得我自私吗?
Do you think I'm selfish?
你?
You?
这是哪门子问题?
What kind of a question is that?
我是说...
I mean, about...
不接受你慷慨的付出
n-not taking you up on your generosity, like...
像是这次旅行...
like going on this trip.
迈克
Michael...
我告诉过你
I already told you,
我所做的一切都是想让你快乐
all I want to do is make you happy.
没错  但是你呢?
Yeah, but what about you? What would...
怎样才能让你快乐?
would make you happy?
我要怎样才快乐?
What would make me happy?
看见你第一次感受巴黎
Seeing you see Paris for the first time,
沿着塞纳河游览
sailing down the... seine on abateau-mouche,
在伟富尔酒店
Having the best meal of our lives at...
或者阿伦·杜卡瑟酒店
"le grand vefour" or, uh...
享受最棒的美食
"Alain Ducasse".
看到你的眼睛因为在跳蚤市场
Seeing your eyes light up
发现小玩具而闪闪发光
when you find some neat little toy in a flea market;
那会使我快乐
That would make me happy.
会使我非常快乐
That would make me very happy.
我希望你快乐
I want you to be happy.
你是说你想去巴黎?
Are you saying you want to go?
既然你已经提前准备
Well, since you already went ahead
规划了一切...
and made the plans and everything...
别为了我委屈自己
Don't do me any favours.
我不会  答应我让我付出点什麽
No, just promise me you'll let me pay for something
偶尔就好
every once in a while.
让你付买面包的钱
I'll let you pay for the baguettes.
不如我们先练练法语吧?
What do you say we practice our French?
这主意不错
This is a good one.
我也喜欢
Oh, I like this one too.
我们家庭很美满
We do make a handsome family.
-对吗?  -没错
-Hein?  -Mmm-hmm.
我们应该把这个放在相框里
We should put this one in a frame...
代替这个
Instead of that one.
布莱恩  他很美
Brian. He's very beautiful.
很多人都这麽觉得
Lots of guys would agree with you.
特别是他的嘴唇
Especially his lips.
亲起来很爽  对吧?
They're quite kissable, yes?
-不!     -你不用担心
-No!     -oh! la la! you needn't worry.
我知道他不喜欢我
I can tell he doesn't like me.
茉蕾妮或者你其他朋友也不喜欢
And neither does Melanie or your other friends...
他们不是不喜欢你
It's not you they don't like.
而是不喜欢我们现在做的事
It's what we're doing.
但这不是他们的决定
But, it's not their decision.
你是个好人  琳赛
Well, you are a wonderful person, Lindsay.
不  这是真的
No, no, no, it's true.
如果不是你
If it weren't for you,
我就要离开美国了
I'd have to leave the states.
而现在我可以留下
Now I'll be able to stay.
亲爱的  是茉蕾妮
Cherie, c'est Melanie.
盖斯应该起来了
Gus should be up from his nap.
我去看看
I'll go check.
我想如果盖斯喜欢他  他一定不错
I guess if Gus likes him, he must be okay.
盖斯知道
Gus knows the difference between who's
混蛋和正常人的区别
an asshole and who's not, right?
没错
Right.
这是什麽?
What are these?
一些照片
Just some photographs.
伪造点感情史很重要
It's important to create a history,
防止移民局随时来拜访
in case immigration ever decides to pay a visit.
天啊
Oh, Jesus!
我不敢相信你在准备这些
I can't believe you're going through with this...
这些  什麽?
This... what?
掩耳盗铃  而且为了谁?
Charade. And for who?
为了一个你不了解的人
Somebody you don't even know.
我告诉过你  是个朋友
I told you, he's a friend.
我不介意是谁
I don't care who he is.
这是我听过最疯狂的理由
It's the most meshugua idea I ever heard of.
我保证如果当时我在的话...
I guarantee you that if I had been here...
但你不在
Well, you're not.
你当时不在
You're not here.
我希望我在
I wish I was.
我很想你  琳
I miss you, Linz.
你只是因为吉拉姆才说的
You're just saying that because of Guillaume.
不是的
No, I'm not.
我每天
I miss you every minute...
每分钟 都想你
of every day.
我对你的思念无时无刻
And if I could miss you more than that, I would.
你以为我不想你吗?
You think I don't miss you?
那我为什麽不在这里?
Then why aren't I here? I mean...
为什麽我们不一起抚养他?
Why aren't we raising our son together?
这没道理
It doesn't make sense.
当时我们都有理由
Well, it did at the time.
你说的一切
I mean, all the things you said,
说我没有投入足够的感情
That I didn't give you enough affection...
我只想着
That I was only concerned about
满足自己的要求
getting my own needs met.
我错了  问题在我
I was wrong. It was me.
我变得妒忌  怨恨
I became... jealous and resentful and...
我要求的太多
I demanded way too much.
你很受伤
You were hurt.
你也是
So were you.
没错
Yeah.
-我想我们只是           -普通人?
-I guess we're only...  -Human?
没错
Yeah.
什麽?
Pardon?
你要喂盖斯吃午餐吗?
Uh, do you want to give Gus his lunch,
还是我来?
Or should I?
我来吧
I'll do it.
大家挥挥手吧
Okay, everybody wave.
来嘛  有点表示
Come on. Put something into it.
你们能做得更好
Oh, you can do better than that.
你以为我们是谁
Who do you think we are,
麦特戴蒙和班艾弗烈克？
Matt Damon and Ben Affleck?
我希望我是啊
I wish.
这样你们可以看到我们
Now you guys can see us
跑遍巴黎的每条街道
running all over the streets of Paris,
就像你们也和我们在那里一样
And it'll be just like you're there with us.
我都等不及了
Oh, I can hardly wait.
那个相机是最贵的型号
That camera is the most expensive model.
我爸有个类似的
My dad has one like it.
-我来拍             -好
- Let me have it.  - All right.
不只是电影里的镜头
Yeah, it not only shoots the movie,
还要有爆米花
It... it makes popcorn to go with it.
我猜不是在大Q超市买的
I guess you didn't get it at the big Q.
大卫喜欢高级货
David likes to go for the high-end.
那你要警惕了
That must keep you on your toes.
是件新夹克吗?
Hey, is that jacket new?
真时髦  迈克
Snazzy, Michael.
BOSS的  还不赖
Boss. Not bad.
我总得有件衣服可穿
Well, I had to have something to wear.
看看这个行李箱
Check out this luggage.
居然还有他的名字在上面
Oh! It's even got his initials on it.
-上帝啊        -才没有
- Oh, my god! - It does not.
我们在走流行路线了  对吧?
My, my. Certainly going in style, aren't we?
你说我不应该拒绝他的
You told me I shouldn't deny him the pleasure.
-他一定高兴疯了  -听着
- Oh, he must be delirious.  - Look...
我说了一起付钱
I offered to help pay,
但他不同意的
But he wouldn't let me.
别担心  小迈
Mmm. Don't worry, Mikey.
你会付出的...
You'll pay...
用这种  或者是另一种方法
One way... or another.
去伍迪吧
Let's go to Woody's.
好  拜  宝贝
Okay. Bye, baby.
拜  迈克
Bye, Michael. See ya.
要听我的建议吗?
You want my advice?
坚持要个劳力士
Hold out for a Rolex.
当然
Of course it did.
妈的  什麽
Fuck! What did?
-另一个蛋蛋      -不是  是你的脸
-The other ball? - No, your face.
另一个蛋蛋...
The other ball...
等等
Wait.
该死  什麽?
Shit! what?
是克里斯·赫伯
It's Chris Hobbs.
谁?
Who's that?
跟你说过的  学校里的混蛋
That asshole from school I told you about.
你可没说他那麽性感
Oh, huh! You didn't tell me he was so hot.
他不该来这
He has no right to be here.
别理他  走吧
Forget him. Let's go.
不行
No.
泰勒
Hey, Taylor.
你在这里干什麽?
What are you doing here?
来看看像你这样的怪物
Checking out the freaks, like you.
在这里  你才是怪物
Huh. Down here you're the freak.
滚开  屁精
Out of the way... faggot. Hey!
布莱恩
Brian!
看到他了吗?
You guys see him?
看到啦
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
我们上同一所学校
We go to school together.
他叫克里斯·赫伯
His name's Chris Hobbs.
他刚刚叫我屁精
He just called me a faggot.
听到吗  克里斯不喜欢屁精
You see, Chris doesn't like faggots.
闭嘴  泰勒
Shut up, Taylor.
或者其实他很喜欢
Or maybe he likes them more than he thinks.
我说闭嘴
I said shut up!
他让我帮他打手枪
He let me jerk him off.
屁精帮克里斯·赫伯打手枪
The faggot gave Chris Hobbs a hand-job.
而且他爱死了
And he loved it.
你死定了
You are fucked!
不敢相信你会这麽做
I can't believe you did that.
支持你  宝贝
You go, baby!
恭喜
Congratulations.
什麽?
What?
给自己找了个真正的敌人
Just made yourself a real enemy.
26046ffa34d64cf1a10c4c942d0f6888